And when, on the other hand, you have folks talking like Julianna Margulies in this next
clip, you're just like, if folks is going to be talking like that, then we need as many
folks as possible countering it.
Who do they think?
They think that Hamas wants them alive?
You know, there was a film being shown by this black lesbian club on Columbia campus,
and they put signs up that said, no Jews allowed.
And as someone who plays a lesbian journalist on the morning show, I'm more offended by it
as a lesbian than I am as a Jew, to be honest with you, because I want to say to them,
you f***ing idiots, you don't exist.
Like, you're even lower than the Jews.
A, you're black, and B, you're gay.
And you're turning your back against the people who support you?
Because Jews, they rally around everybody.
Right.
It's such a complex...
Now, I don't believe for 2.2 seconds that black women in a lesbian organization would take
the time to find posters and Sharpies to ostracize Jewish folks from a viewing.
Pics or it didn't happen.
Pics with the black lesbians there, or it didn't happen.
Because can anyone confirm this for me?
As a Columbia University alumnus, can anyone confirm that for me?
Columbia University lesbian group disinvites Zionists for movie night.
Now I'm going to say something that most people already know, but it just needs to be reiterated
all the time.
All Jewish people are not Zionists.
Zionists have identified themselves as people who are in support of a genocide of Palestinians
in order for the existence of a Jewish state.
So if there's an event and someone puts up a sign saying,
no racists allowed, okay?
Or let me get even more specific.
No white supremacists allowed.
That is not a sign that says, no white people allowed.
That is a sign that addresses this particular political ideology.
Ideology and that an ideology that seeks to harm others.
And so they're allowed to say, we don't want that represented in our space.